<resources>
    <string name="app_name">University of Calicut</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="about_fragment_title">About</string>
    <string name="demo_fragment_title_one">Home</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="demo_two">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pareeksha_bhavan">Directorate of Admission</string>
    <string name="title_fragment_pareekshabavan">Pareeksha Bhavan</string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">DetailActivity</string>
    <string name="home_desc">The University of Calicut is the largest University in Kerala. Established in the year 1968, it is the second university to be set up in Kerala. The University aims to nurture excellence in education and research in its catchment areas of Northern Kerala, historically consigned to the periphery of Kerala’s academic map. The University lays its emphasis on fostering quality human resource and promoting productive research that benefit both local communities and wider humanity.The University was created through a Government plan bifurcating Kerala University. As per the plan, the four post-graduate departments of the University of Kerala operating in Calicut were annexed to the new University along with fifty four constituent colleges spread across seven northern districts. With ‘Nirmaya Karmana Sree’ as it motto, the University has been able to surmount all challenges and emerge as the largest residential cum affiliating University in Kerala. With 30 post graduate departments and 373 affiliated colleges it has become a beacon of hope and enlightenment for hundreds of thousands of young men and women in North Kerala.</string>


    <string name="chancellor">"Chancellor \nHon.Kerala Governor"</string>
    <string name="chanc">"Sri.P Sathasivam"</string>
    <string name="pro_chancellor">"Pro Chancellor \nHon. Minister for Education,Kerala"</string>
    <string name="pc">"Sri Abdu Rabb"</string>
    <string name="vice_chancellor">"Vice–Chancellor"</string>
    <string name="vc">"Dr. M Abdul Salam"</string>
    <string name="pro_vice_chancellor">"Pro-Vice-Chancellor "</string>
    <string name="pvc">"Prof.K.Raveendranath"</string>

    <string name="title_activity_authorities">Authorities</string>
    <string name="heading_authorities">Central Confidential and General Section</string>
    <string name="cntrl_exam">Dr. V V Georgekutty\nController of Examination:\nContact:0494–2400291</string>
    <string name="gen_section">Mohanakrishnan C S\nContact:  0494-2407202\nEmail: jce1@universityofcalicut.info</string>
    <string name="heading_authorities1">B.A. and Oriental Title Courses</string>
    <string name="gen_section1">Anuja Balakrishnan\nContact:   0494-2407223, 2407229\nEmail: jce2@universityofcalicut.info</string>
    <string name="heading_authorities2">B.Com and B.B.A</string>
    <string name="gen_section2">P P Rajendran\nContact:   0494-2407284\nEmail: jce3@universityofcalicut.info</string>
    <string name="heading_authorities3">B.Sc., B.C.A (EPR-1)</string>
    <string name="gen_section3">E. P Pavithran\nContact:  0494-2407214\nEmail: jce4@universityofcalicut.info</string>
    <string name="heading_authorities4">P.G. Courses and B.Ed. /M.Ed. Courses</string>
    <string name="gen_section4">Suresh .K.K\nContact:  0494-2407206, 2401130\nEmail: jce5@universityofcalicut.info</string>
    <string name="heading_authorities5">B.Tech. Courses</string>
    <string name="gen_section5">Praveena R, O.B Jayanthi\nContact:  0494-2407234, 2407215\nEmail: jce6@universityofcalicut.info</string>
    <string name="title_activity_syllabus">Syllabus</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="title_activity_result">Result</string>
    <string name="title_activity_time_table">Time Table</string>
    <string name="title_activity_diedu">Distance Education</string>
    <string name="title_activity_online_reg">Online Registration</string>
    <string name="title_activity_plcmnt">Placement Portal</string>
    <string name="online_payment">Online Payment</string>
    <string name="plcmnt_heading">Placement portal</string>
    <string name="plcmnt_desc">This web portal is an initiative of the University of Calicut to help all its students to search for jobs and manage their careers. It also helps recruiters to identify the right candidates for their manpower requirements. The University turns out a large pool of talent every year. Over a hundred thousand students pass out each year in diverse branches of learning like engineering, IT/computer science, management, core sciences, humanities, Commerce, health care, pharmacy, media, travel and tourism, economics, hotel management, catering science, etc.\nThis portal offers free registration to recruiters and job aspirants. Since, the web portal enables registered recruiters to access a large database of registered candidates (graduates, post graduates and Doctorates of the University and its 380 affiliated colleges), the recruiters can search availability of candidates with the required competence and schedule their visits to the campus for recruitment and selection. \nThe University believes in creating lasting relationships with corporate and other recruiters based on trust and mutuality. The Placement Cell of the University is entrusted with the responsibility of serving both the job seekers and job givers

</string>

    <string name="dist_edu_heading">School of distance education</string>
    <string name="dist_edu_desc">Established in 1981, the School has emerged as a major distance education provider in Kerala. Annually about 30 thousand students enrol for the programmes of the School available under two streams – Regular and Open. Regular Stream Courses are meant for those who wish to pursue their studies though distance education mode provided they satisfy the conditions prescribed for admission to the graduate and postgraduate programmes offered in colleges affiliated to the University.\nCurrently, the School offers 16 graduate courses, 13 postgraduate courses and two diploma courses. Students admitted to these courses are provided printed study materials. All students are expected to attend contact programmes and training sessions arranged regularly at notified centres. \nThe School has approved 18 educational institutions in different States of India to enrol students for various courses offered by the School. Also, the School has six approved overseas centres at Sharjah, Abu Dhabi , Doha , Kuwait and Bahrain</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
</resources>
